Hello, my name is Sarah, I run a boutique publishing house here in the Sunshine Coast
called Hinterland Co in Australia.
And I first contacted Omer maybe three to four months ago in the team at Zumetrix
to help me to finalize the billing system for a client portal.
And it was a subscription service, so it was a little bit difficult and Omer has simplified
everything, created great handover notes for me and got the whole thing ticking along
really well.
What has really stood out to me is his very easy going attitude and he always seems to
be available for my annoying questions and answers them with a lot of patience.
So his after sales support continues to this day and is greatly appreciated.
Thank you Omer.